<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NYC Icarus Hub</title>
    <description>We are the local New York City Icarus Project chapter</description>
    <link>http://nycicarus.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://nycicarus.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 01:19:36 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 01:19:36 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Icarus Workshop @ Blue Stockings</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This month’s exciting Icarus Project event will feature a Forum Theater style play, developed and performed by members of the Icarus community. The scenes will investigate struggles regarding moments of mental crises, taken from the actor’s and writer’s real life experiences. Audience members will help problem solve through reenactment and discussion, using Mad Maps style community strategies. Let’s talk about how we can advocate for ourselves with doctors, employers, and teachers, as well as with our loved ones. Join us for this empowering and fun experience inspired by Theater of the Oppressed and the power of our local NYC Icarus community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When: Wed March 4th, 7pm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where: Bluestockings Bookstore, Café, &amp;amp; Activist Center, 172 Allen St, New York, New York 10002 (https://goo.gl/maps/5eCPE)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facebook event: https://www.facebook.com/events/858455424220310&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventbrite event: https://www.eventbrite.com/e/mad-maps-forum-theater-tickets-4360835376&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Icarus Project is a support network and media project by and for people who experience the world in ways that are often diagnosed as mental illness. We advance social justice by fostering mutual aid practices that reconnect healing and collective liberation. We transform ourselves through transforming the world around us.” - The Icarus Project Mission Statement 2014&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;http://theicarusproject.net&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://nycicarus.github.io/2015/03/04/March-Workshop/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nycicarus.github.io/2015/03/04/March-Workshop/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
